hi guys and welcome back to my channel
my name is annalise and in today's video
i'm testing out the
the as i am curl color these are six new
colors that as i am just dropped i
decided to go with the color purple
today
shoe i put out videos on monday
so don't forget to subscribe to my
channel click on that bell to get
notified exactly when you go uploads a
new video
and if you want to see how i use this
special purple color on my hair
make sure you keep on watching so
i got three colors i got the red one
they call it hot red they call it
passion purple
and the other one is sassy silver now
i'm a sassy girl so i shoulda
the silver one but i'm hesitating so i
think i'm gonna go with the purple one
for the sake of the video and try
something different because
i always tend to go for the natural
stuff so let me just
try a purple color these were gifted by
as i am so
thank you as i am i don't think they're
available in the netherlands yet by the
time i'm uploading this video
it might be i will uh link it down below
if i find a website that
ships to the netherlands or ships in the
netherlands
so i already washed my hair so i will
put all the products that i use
for wash day down below i use that
shampoo and air conditioner though the
new black jamaican castor oil line
because i wanted to try that restore and
repair i think it's called restore and
repair line
i wanted to try that anyway so and i
will put the leave-in conditioner and
the gel that i use
down below my hair is already washed uh
so my hair
i don't know why i'm talking am i
yelling let me know in the comments if
i'm yelling
i don't want to yell i don't like
yelling because i i always talk loud so
i'm gonna try to
bring it down a couple notches but
anyway yeah today we're gonna go with
the purple one we're gonna leave this
for another time a few years ago i had
my tips blonde
and that was the last time i i dyed my
hair
i'm super excited to try this hence why
they sent me this i was like oh girl
yo i need these so anyway
talking too much we're gonna get into
this uh color
i'm gonna section my hair in two parts i
have a lower part
in the upper part right girl right
should i get gloves i think so let's
see okay before applying
it's important to cleanse the hair using
as i am
shampoo and or co-wash spray
water oh girl i just did my own leave-in
conditioner
uh either apply as i am classic leave-in
before coloring or another one
towel dry hair okay towel dry and leave
them not dripping before applying
use gloves to apply color so we're gonna
get some gloves girl
direction section hair off and apply to
damp hair
from roots to tip use a generous amount
based on thickness of hair twist or rake
through hair
for desired style great for twist out
coils
wash and goes and rotate girl we don't
want a wiring girl that's me
so i'm gonna get some gloves wait
i know it's gonna transfer in the
beginning so hence i'm
wearing a black shirt so get yourself an
old shirt or
old towel girl i'm so excited
so this is the color i don't know if you
guys can see it
this is the color purple right
it smells good though smells good i was
confused like
is this a leave-in conditioner is this a
gel but they call this a color gel
that provides a medium hold and last one
wash so it's just one wash and it is a
gel so i think you can use this after a
leave-in conditioner
that's what they say because i was com i
was hella confused like
how should i use this is this a gel is
this a leave-in conditioner is it just
something is it just a color
i don't know so we're not going to try
it girl they have six colors there's an
orange one a blue one
and a gold one but anyway so
here it is let's get started
generous amount i think is this a
generous amount
i don't know
who good ciao
i'm looking in the mirror to see how
this goes
you guys and you should apply it from
the roots to the tips
from the root to the tip honey ciao
i'm so excited i'm so excited
so excited you guys look at this
oh
i should use sparkly
hey guys what do you guys think oh
so okay so let me just turn around
okay let me put some more for the sake
of this video
so i'm excited to see how it um
will dry because i'm gonna air dry my
hair i'm not gonna
i'm not gonna diffuse my hair i'm gonna
let it air dry i still have volume
or nuts
since it is a gel and i'm putting a
generous amount in it
i don't know if i'm gonna do some volume
shimmer
yeah oh yeah they said from the
root to the tips
putting a little bit i'm putting a
little bit more
you got oh yeah
you should definitely put some gloves on
girl because i saw another youtuber
doing this and she had like
a hard time getting it off of her hand
so
you guys gloves
i'm a purple girl who would have thought
purple honey
baby little bit more it smells so good
it smells like
you'd be smelling like tropical islands
girl i think this is enough i think this
is enough
i don't want to push it
it goes purple and it for one washing
this is
cute i like reviewing products but this
is something different
i'm gonna let this dry i'm gonna stay in
the house so i cannot manipulate this
with the weather
and and i'm gonna come back and show you
guys the
end result let me just show you guys how
it looks
yeah okay so i'll see you guys in a few
hours
oh my god this is oh my god this is
purple
imagine okay i'm now in the house but i
have to leave in like a few minutes i'll
take the camera with me and just
um show you guys how it looks outside
because the sun is shining and
we're gonna see now it's
purple alright okay okay my hair is
still not 100 dry
as i shake my hair um
i see it's rubbing off a a little bit on
my hands
a little bit i don't know if you guys
can see it
if it's picking up a little bit
on the tip of my hands maybe sleep with
a bunnette or
i don't know you're gonna have to figure
that one out but
overall i think it's cute i think it's
very nice i'm
super excited to see how this will show
up
in daylight but overall i'm happy with
this color though
um what i will say is it's like a gel
so it can leave a hard cast on your hair
you just have to scrunch your hair or
just
you know take the hard cast out take the
hard cast out
girl because that's not cute
but i think when this is fully dry like
100 dry
this will look stunning
so yeah you have to be careful with
transfer um
i wouldn't wear this with white my hair
being this length maybe if it was
shorter i would do it but that's me
yo this is the color outside
as you can see it's out there already
yeah i think this would be fun if i
would go to a festival or
if i would go somewhere if i would go to
a daytime party or a festival or
something like that i think it would
be hey you honey so yeah
so let me i'm in the car right now and
this is the next day so i slept with a
bunnette on my head and
as you can see it's still in there and
it hasn't transferred
yet so happy so that was it for this
video you guys i hope that you guys
liked it and i hope that i got to
explain how i uh
use this uh curl color on my hair let me
know what color you would get
the next color that i want to try is the
silver one
definitely trying silver one so yeah let
me know down in the comments what color
you would use
and um and if you have using what color
would you recommend for darker hair
don't forget to thumbs up this video
subscribe to my channel to see more of
mwah and hair related content and some
hauls and stuff like that
but yeah i'll see you guys in my next
video have an amazing morning afternoon
or evening wherever you are and i wish
you guys a blessed week bye guys